<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>CD373 Fall 2015: Dustin Stone</title>
    <description>Pursuing B.S. in Computer Science @ University of Texas at Austin</description>
    <link>http://dustinstone.github.io</link>
    <atom:link href="http://dustinstone.github.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>Software Engineering Is Good for You.</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Software Engineering is – in a few important ways – unlike any other class I have taken here at the
University. It carries a writing flag as an upper division CS course and promises to equip us with
tools and technologies to make us more employable outside of school. Professor Downing also has a
unique  way of asking for participation from every student in the class… so pay attention! You
&lt;strong&gt;will&lt;/strong&gt; be called  on!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;The writing bit&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I am happy that this blog will force me to improve my writing style via weekly feedback from other
students. Writing is an effective form of communication and is essential even as a developer.
Whether you’re writing emails, cover letters, or a research thesis, your writing is a reflection of
you. Also, well- documented code is essential to a team. Nobody wants to figure out how your code
works or doesn’t  work the hard way (after weeks of trying)&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;The software engineering bit&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As developers, we have committed to being life-long learners. Technologies may come and go, but it
is a  valuable skill to keep up with the current best practices. It is equally important to ask why
practices may  be preferable over another in class, I have already benefitted from it. Software
Engineering will be challenging  but challenges are valuable learning experiences. It already
appears as though Professor Downing will encourage  good habits like focusing in class, documenting
effectively, reflecting weekly, and diving into new technologies.  I’m looking forward to it!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4&gt;Tip o&amp;#39; the week&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This article &lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2015/07/what-you-miss-when-you-take-notes-on-your-laptop&quot;&gt;What You Miss When You Take Notes on Your Laptop&lt;/a&gt; 
from Harvard Business Review was passed along to me this week so I thought I&amp;#39;d do the same. You may 
benefit from this in class. If nothing else, it&amp;#39;s an interesting read.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 30 Aug 2015 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>http://dustinstone.github.io/Software-Engineering-Is-Good-for-You/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://dustinstone.github.io/Software-Engineering-Is-Good-for-You/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>